<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<p:sld xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:p="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/presentationml/2006/main"><p:cSld><p:spTree><p:nvGrpSpPr><p:cNvPr id="1" name=""/><p:cNvGrpSpPr/><p:nvPr/></p:nvGrpSpPr><p:grpSpPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="0" cy="0"/><a:chOff x="0" y="0"/><a:chExt cx="0" cy="0"/></a:xfrm></p:grpSpPr><p:sp><p:nvSpPr><p:cNvPr id="2" name="Title 1"/><p:cNvSpPr><a:spLocks noGrp="1"/></p:cNvSpPr><p:nvPr><p:ph type="title"/></p:nvPr></p:nvSpPr><p:spPr/><p:txBody><a:bodyPr/><a:lstStyle/><a:p><a:pPr algn="ctr"/><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>Literature Review</a:t></a:r></a:p></p:txBody></p:sp><p:sp><p:nvSpPr><p:cNvPr id="3" name="Content Placeholder 2"/><p:cNvSpPr><a:spLocks noGrp="1"/></p:cNvSpPr><p:nvPr><p:ph idx="1"/></p:nvPr></p:nvSpPr><p:spPr/><p:txBody><a:bodyPr><a:normAutofit fontScale="70000" lnSpcReduction="20000"/></a:bodyPr><a:lstStyle/><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0"/><a:t>The Cyber Security war will be brutal to crush, as even the caretakers of the law have discovered it to be a weapon to accomplish unlawful additions. This is clear as certain states generally draw in the administrations of programmers to achieve insidious plans. It is disconcerting to see various nations utilizing complex malware, skewer phishing, and refusal to convey administration against each other. I see this as some kind of digital conflict or digital psychological warfare, which unquestionably would be deadlier than illegal intimidation. In 2011, the pentagon noticed that any demonstration of assault or harm showing up from another nation is a potential demonstration of war (</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0" err="1"/><a:t>Alam</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0"/><a:t>, </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" i="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>et al. </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0"/><a:t>2019). Mill operator depicted this as the militarization of digital assaults utilizing profoundly prepared programmers to get essential assets and data. Likewise, the coordinated idea of digital wrongdoing has made the battle against digital wrongdoing troublesome. As indicated by a survey in 2012, coordinated hacking established 80% of digital wrongdoing exercises. In 2014, a first of its sort, a gigantic and modern assault was dispatched against Sony. This degree of assault mirrors the profoundly and strategical hierarchical construction of a coordinated assault ascribed to the Korean government. Theophany alluded to this nature of assault as data fighting, that is, one that includes nations, government and large enterprises in a piece to upset public safety. </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0" err="1"/><a:t>Ferrillo</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-IN" dirty="0"/><a:t> highlighted a new delivery by the FBI expressing that China alone represented 95% of information breaks from far-off nations. Investigating information and figures coming about because of effective digital assaults and information breaks, one can, without much of a stretch, presume that battling digital assault would require enormous monetary planning and ceaseless spending.</a:t></a:r></a:p></p:txBody></p:sp></p:spTree><p:extLst><p:ext uri="{BB962C8B-B14F-4D97-AF65-F5344CB8AC3E}"><p14:creationId xmlns:p14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/powerpoint/2010/main" val="1519964015"/></p:ext></p:extLst></p:cSld><p:clrMapOvr><a:masterClrMapping/></p:clrMapOvr></p:sld>